That's
[music]
that's
Hello guys my name is Jyoti Agarwal and if you
can join the last channel today we are going to talk about
insurance company its
insurance company it has not been cooking rice for a long time
I thought now the time has come
when we should maybe inch and now we have
a good thing in it that we
should study school boys so now in size later this
session has also been kept it is called in size
pills playlist has been made for it and
this is the reason because there are some
tractors which I am seeing who are
saying that maybe the
time has come for insurance company to run
you will notice that some time ago
such people from here were very tasty sewing money pressure
live and your SBI Life was listed
in the market so they were seeing a lot of boom
now that boom is because somewhere
or the other everyone is getting a lot of business entry
penetration is very high and all these
stores are running in between at that time when it comes to
insurance let me tell you in advance
that the penetration inside is not very
high
because if you look at the country the functional literacy is
very low which  People pay
very less income tax, so if we look at that,
I think a lot of
people have insurance. It can be availed from doctors here and there in
developed countries, but
even there it is not the case that 90% of the
people are insured. I can only
believe that for a country like India,
if you have insurance in lower single digits, then
higher single digits or
very weak countries sleep, insurance will be extended up to double digits. According to me,
I don't think India can achieve
25-30% insurance penetration. According to that,
I don't think that the population is
going to take insurance. Now, there is
definitely a skin problem from the government's side, under
Ayushman Bharat, under which a lot of people
get a lot of benefits from the internet,
and still a lot of people do
not even select it, whereas we should, so this
part becomes the front part which is private
insurance or proper insurance coverage, there is
insurance coverage under Torch
and on Breakup Channel, we saw that
such people take it compulsory, but health
insurance.  You have got life insurance,
then there are all these big insurances which you can take
from the life insurance company, there is a
cardiac care plan, there is a cancer care plan, so
people do not refer to all these things normally,
people think that they will
not fall ill, why do we need it, in fact there is a
tax benefit of it because you get
deductions while filing income tax,
they will do it, this is a big reason why
people take insurance, it is very surprising, people are
not taking insurance because of insurance, they are taking it to save money, they are
taking it to save tax, that
dormant has to be said and
incentives, why should
people go towards a good product, well because
now they get it done in half an hour,
like we saw some simple which was not
salva, then the way people's expenses were happening,
like medical bills, it is the best,
if you are not constipated by insurance then it was causing a
lot of pain, somewhere or the other,
all of you will suffer from diseases, as the pain
increases, everyone will suffer, so somewhere or the other you have to
believe that we will need insurance,
so show your top  Up lines a lot of
things come up now I am talking to you about one thing so
recently what happened is that
personal health insurance is run by irrigation and flood
and I got a voice mail
that you know now you will have to increase us in the company
Vihar has been wrapped up application with the
regulator of ball there is insurance regulator
we have submitted this application with them also that
fingers from Paytm to Bigg Boss Gomez and
due to many things we also got infections
etc. in this it did not suit us the
old princes that were going on so
the calling happened in health insurance so this is the
premium tips of theirs this is my chest my
earth insurance they
also charge me this ton weight when I go to the gym and in my memory the
premium which I will tell you in part so
2 years ago when I
took this cloth insurance they used to sell dangerous
or drops something and I got
back 2001 period of two years because
every year those who go then press whatever bills there are
and
give money to the companies which will inform so it was
my little mistake insurance is not according to me
but the land is drowning back  If I had
fought with these people without paying for going to the gym, my
no claim bonus would have been lost and the
amount of insurance coverage, the back cover,
which keeps increasing, along with that, this
year I got an email and the
premium has been increased a lot, if I renew it for 2 years, then
I have to pay 80 plus,
which I or Hussain had
paid 2 years ago, right, this has also increased in the last
2 years, it will be a time pass, let's
assume it is big, my wife is twenty six,
so it is not that I am in this roof, or I
am somewhere else, that my cream will
rise so sharply, so this has happened somewhere
due to inflation and other things,
you should definitely comment on this, the fat or
insurance that we have seen saying, now with this by
chance, yesterday when I was
checking the charts etc., I saw my
wife looking at it as if in this, then they will
discuss all of us,
how can there be two questions inside, if I
provide you extra information technology,
which charts  But we will go ahead and understand all the things
but this is a small thing, the
insurance premium has increased, so
we have at least this much right, the insurance company is
like a jerk, Aunty plays like a snake and
penetration will happen, now I have already
told you, I think that
not everyone has that much access, according to the Indian market,
people think that it is a
matter of three, so people think that
if there is so much internet, everyone can see,
less pigmentation starts coming, movement starts coming in the staff,
people start justifying the
revolution and they will do this last
yesterday sister for all the comments and
someday your cycle will come here, so please
explain to me how it is installed, it does not seem to be a problem, I have
not given much time to this insurance company, but it will
not break, so the share price,
somewhere or the other, it is a line wise correction, but it is
going on, so now these creams are increasing,
I came to know on the health insurance site that the
premium is increasing,
I did not pay attention to other places,
if car insurance is not at home then I
looked at both sides carefully, but
in a particular case, I got a mail or two days later, so
definitely  Tell me the Samsung
Duos price change with the taken place and you will have to
renew your policy a little bit on that only you know somewhere or the other you will have to renew your policy there is a thirty day
grace period this is that explain we are
increasing this everything is there just
play that the film increased those instruments might not be
Goswami and reduction goes so there is no
problem with that by the letter it does
not suit the consumer from America also so the
share holder is doing
some item syrup and discrimination with me who is
running the business that if the
insurance companies do not earn money then it will
switch off like an insurance policy then it will be because of the
bank then the whole system gets spoiled
otherwise somewhere or the other so there is no
such problem in that big
companies are doing things recording to do the thing
communists also run and somewhere or the other
regulators are sitting who are guiding
who are regulating the market of Hussain
so now we see and went up and according to the
calculation there is an Edison movement happening inside them
and is it just this small in more eyes  You
could
see a very clever TV inside these talks. I
should give you some updates here before
climbing to the heights and moving on the screen.
So I would say that I think this
small group can translate into a very large one because now they have seen many
discoms going with rising values. If they are increasing prices, then
these taxes will increase.
Normally, people do not switch their insurance provider. I have to take
this point to
the largest private insurance
player because the network is not the biggest.
Secondly, you know what happens is that the
bigger the tree you sleep with, the better
your book is somewhere. Because
many people here
go with very cheap insurance companies. They are not that
big. Right, I am not giving anything to anyone whose business
model is bad, but I have
seen in a number of developed markets, like the United
States of America, where this small
information becomes computer class, then we have to be
careful somewhere.
Anyway, in the stock market, prices
generate pimples and wrinkles for me, so
I and  I don't
want to take stock market and money
market research on an internet site. Many things are
not in our control. Keep this place in gold.
This deficiency in the agreement will not work. So,
exams are going to be printed on my
file. I tried to install it. As it is,
my body is a little expensive from some small
insurance companies. Body effect me. And
somewhere I got a price in
which these people charge me for going to the gym.
So my left Williams
and in the last two years before this, there was free jinx
and comment. It will cost only 10 something.
Waste is very charming and there is no such thing.
Plus, Saif thinks that
due to this plant going to the gym, their death is getting
extra for free. Now I will talk about the
stop line in which people do not get money for going to the gym.
Next, Master Cigarette, then
see, decently big ones are decreasing,
so we will look at all those things. But let's go to
our charges and see
how the charts of these insurance companies are
moving. So, let's keep this
estimate in focus. Let's
look at the charts of the other three insurance companies as well. If you take a
chance, and gas trading
which I  If you don't follow, then
I have recently set many alarms for chemical stocks based
on the charts of the teams and
I have posted the charts, then you can
see that in the ongoing decline,
especially in these mass chemical
stocks, Allama Iqbal Azim
printing and Lakshmi Deepak Knight, there is a
big vacation in these, so according to these, there are
hotspots, you can see the lines etc. here, you can
see your stop loss and
somewhere you can take some guidance from
there, so let's continue the discussion on your screen, you
can see that the
chart of ICICI Lombard is open and I had made
lines etc. within ICC Lombard, you
can see on this
how the range is tied, there was an upward
movement in the chart, there was a chaotic birth of the giver,
planted A is going on from the number cart,
somewhere on all these charts, Mumbai
is visible and first of all, when we were
trying to catch the movement, you
saw Godwa Patan but  This is a very clear
printout. If you want to say something about the hotspot turn, you should
not do it, but you can leave it, but by
resistance, the mind is formed. And
after that, see, you also saw a movement inside it,
but since then the range has been coming back, so we
expect that when this range will be broken, and recently an
attempt was made to break it, but it did
not come back very fast. And as the range does, we are
fully hopeful that we can see a
good movement coming here,
such a romantic share Chanakya's beans.
And now let's talk about it, we are
discussing it shallowly. So first of all, let's
look at this stitching. And after that, we can
look at the rest of the life insurance companies. So,
inside this, you can see that there is a
pattern on the independence.
Normally, I teach a lot. So then, to
say, this drawing and lines of key remain on the
chaat. And after that, there was
a cup, then there was a anger in the middle also.
But this correction,
Renu Pandey and I are going on. If I
draw a line, you can see that at
some of the fastest  The whole inch and extra is not working,
so let's look at the rest of the shirts as well, let's go
to Vice
President Life,
you can also see the A potential of,
this means left right, so you must be understanding this thing,
3 inches and in this shirt till now we have
seen an extra cylinder blast
here and after that, when all three bowled,
it still went up in a good mood and
still you have stopped here, it will
not take support here, it will be a matter of seeing, give
support, good, for this you have a
problem in such a matter, as a rule,
this trick should have been used, the year is
also coming down a little, so you are
getting support here, then you are getting support here also,
so till where does it go,
what does ultimate support do, so this is what
we have also seen in the conversation stocks,
now our last one which is left for us is SBI
Life, we will also look at 10th Life Insurance, it is the
last player among the standalone insurance companies, in its chart you
can see that there was a slight rise first,
then it started falling and then it started going up
and  Now you should
also see the line partner, the net may be running a little slow
or the trading is going on that day, there is a
little bump on that basis, today
my butter lines are already normal,
like I tell you, keep quiet and
leave a lot of thoughts and see, if you were doing anything etc. then the
lines are formed normally, if you
click on the chart clearly what is
happening, you can see
that it has worked and after that now the
encounter has started, if you look at the chart of SBI Life, then it
is much better than other insurance companies, and
if you want to see any company, then
Lifelines Lite or HDFC Life
is very good, but in this video
my focus was on the
basis of Vikas Loot in the beginning on WhatsApp, it is on the
basis of 30%, I thought that
we should talk about it, so let me say that when a
general insurance company provides you health
insurance, motor insurance, then
we have to keep in mind that
if I tell you, it is visible in it, then it
cuts the upper levels  If it is 10:00
then a line can definitely be made here, a good
fortune of investment grade to keep in the portfolio for a long time, see when it was in here and
after that an adoption has been made that the whole choice should be
very high, people do
not get insurance, people will get insurance,
people will keep getting insurance for years, just insurance insurance inch
and this was being heard and the
place was going on with all the shirts, there was very bad admission, there would be a lot, there was a lot of
ignoring WhatsApp, it is surprising that when this tree was
cut, the group ended, on the contrary, the
expenses of these people increased a lot, right,
after that a nation and after that now keep an
eye on this range 520 shirt, definitely keep an eye on it, keep watching it
closely, if
you ever feel that it is going to happen and you
can catch the mood then it will be very good,
rest of the telegraph updates will keep coming about it,
if ever I feel that
general travel is coming in the insurance sector
then those things should be the
first thing you message on telegram friends, it would be
necessary to set it here, it is very easy, if we
make videos then friends  Today we are in that,
so if you
want to join the Telegram channel, there is a one time
membership in this note, you are most welcome to stay
connected with the YouTube channel, here
also we will keep running napkins continuously in quality hours,
meanwhile on this side of Dhan, there is
a notification with 150 grams committee and when
we do Nati discussion, we get
unlimited quotes. Whatever doubts you have, you can
ask anything from that, we will keep it and in that you have to
say that we should discuss it, thank
you, so much for this Vansh Vansh fashion, did you
like the website Madhulika, you must have learned something new,
if you liked the video then like it,
subscribe to the channel
and also share it
on WhatsApp group Telegram group, it will
also help your people, why can't I fit in like this,
how am I thinking, if we do it then at
least we can follow the charts, there is so much
subjectivity in the charts, we have drawn lines and spent the
right time, thank you so much, I
mention by agree